装飾
頬色に
茜さす陽は柔らかに
弾けた
射用に
僕らは目も開かぬまま
It is so painful I don't want to be out yet
First, my eyes were taken down
U Supposed to begin withcourse
But for most, I have to 끝בה
By dancing
will be upward
明るさ誰かにも見つ for me.
もう何も見えよう.
僕は僕を一つは愛せたのに
車両に気づけば目もわかぬまま
雫な揺らぎの中
僕らは目もわかぬまま
Hey, girl! Sorry I fell asleep.
What does like even mean?
This is just like the I don't hate her sort of like, right?
Nothing more nefarious than that.
It's not like I want to go out with her or anything. No way.
Love and infatuation and all that is just the brain bugging out anyway.
Like some sort of mental illness.
The sort that leads plenty of sad mucks to ruin their lives.
I would never allow myself to succumb to that.
Chi wrote on it yesterday, so now it's your turn today, Moeiko.
Wait, we're taking turns on this?
Mm-hmm.
Is she staring at Yamada?
Wait, what am I seeing?
Is she trying to sneak that out of class?
Is it to feed the abandoned dogs and cats?
Like some scene out of a manga?
Hey Yamada, where's your milk?
I drank it already.
That's fast.
At least, I thought it might be.
But it was just to make some peruche.
Come on, though, again?
Why does she always pick things she has to make herself?
Save that stuff for home!
Don't you need a bowl to make that anyway?
Huh?
Sh-shouldn't you be careful?
There's no bowls, so there's no choice.
Must be some in the home-ed room.
Oh, you're right.
Then, go fetch me one.
Damn this girl!
Wait!
I'm kidding!
Let's go together.
Yamada, you sure do love stuff that's a pain to make like that netter netter netter nay.
Yeah, I'm on a bit of a cooking kick.
Cooking?
Did she think making netter netter netter nay and peruche count as cooking?
Ugh, Yamada.
It's locked.
Seems like.
Now, wait a second!
The science lab?
Shh.
There's someone in the other room.
Better keep quiet.
Huh?
You're obsessed!
Shh!
Measuring stuff out is key!
Sorry!
Now then.
Hmm.
Here.
Stay low so we don't draw any attention.
Mm-hmm.
What the heck sort of situation is this anyway?!
All done now!
Shoot!
We have no spoons!
Give me your finger!
Huh?
Come on!
Mm!
How is it?
It's alright.
Oh!
This is all I get.
What are you kids doing?
Oh!
We just forgot something here!
You forgot what?
Huh?
Come on.
How is it?
It's, uh, all right.
This is all I get?
What are you kids doing?
We, uh, just forgot something here.
You forgot what?
Huh?
That's, uh...
It's just Peruche!
Ichikawa!
Sure got an earful for that stunt.
Unbelievable.
Hmm? Again?
Hey, I just...
Didn't realize the window was open.
That's what you get for being a space case.
Come get it with me!
Get it yourself!
Rin, did you apologize?
Gah, it wasn't like I meant to do it, you know?
That may be, but you could at least apologize to her.
She might think you did it on purpose if you don't shove your pride down and say anything.
Oh, come on.
Gross.
Never could stand these cat fights.
What happened?
You never used to be like this back in elementary school.
You're the one who changed Serena!
You're so lame!
Hanging all over her!
Huh?
Hey, uh...
Guess it must look like that to people who don't really know Yamada.
Yamada herself seems like she cares the least, though.
What's Kanaoia doing here?
Is she here to say sorry?
Guess I better excuse myself and...
Hey!
Isn't this hilarious?
I swapped faces with the poster behind me.
Look at this one.
See?
I swapped faces with my cute little dog.
Creepy, isn't it?
Uh-huh.
This is really not the time!
Shoot!
I'm getting in the way here!
Safe!
Wanna take one with me?
Uh...
Uh…
No, I don't like that stuff.
No, huh?
Oh…
Uh…
that's so-
wait…
Uh…
uh…
No?
I don't like that stuff.
Uh…
Uh, no, huh?
Damn it all!
Shh.
Has she been watching this whole time?
Look at this, Kanaoya.
Ever use this?
Hey, hi there, Yamada.
Didn't see you.
Ever used what?
This face swapping app.
That was really big a while back, yeah?
Well, it's big with me right now.
Wanna take one?
If you want.
But you know you're just gonna be ugly looking swapping with me.
Show some modesty.
Ready?
All done.
Hey, what's with the weird-ass face?
Hee hee.
Oh, you know, I could've made an even weirder face if my nose wasn't messed up.
Oh, well.
Sorry.
I really am.
What?
Why's that?
Hey, what are you sorry for?
I'm the one who hit you with the ball.
You hit me?
She didn't even know?
It's no big deal.
I should be the one apologizing.
Hey, want some of my snacks?
Gone.
Oh, I bet I have some candy.
Sheesh.
Oh, you're here too?
Would you please get down here and help me?
See?
What are you even talking about, huh?
You're such an idiot.
Yeah, well...
I'm sorry as well.
I got a little too worked up.
What?
Why's that?
What is it you're sorry for?
Dude, what gives?
Acting like her doesn't make you any cuter, you know?
Ought to thank you too, Ichikawa.
What?
Why is that?
What is it you're sorry for?
People sure are worried about Yamada's nose, huh?
I guess in the scheme of things, it only makes sense.
She's a model, after all.
Not that she seems to care one bit.
Seriously, what's her deal?
Oh!
Wow!
Look at you with your fancy bike.
Lucky you, eh?
She sounds like she's about to mug me.
Wanna give me a ride?
Huh?
Um, d-do I?
Take you to where?
What?
You actually will?
Don't ask if you don't mean it!
Then tomorrow, a snack shop, please.
Where's that?
Don't girls usually sit with their legs to the side?
I almost forgot!
Hang on.
Poppy Go?
I never would have dreamed, in all my miserable life, that I split a pack of poppy goat with a girl!
Here!
Right, of course.
This is Yamada we're talking about.
Uh, yeah, thanks.
What the heck kind of reaction was she looking for?
Isn't this whole riding together a bit too sudden and grown up, though?
Don't you ever have club practice or anything?
No, I'm just in the data processing club.
We only meet once a week.
Sudden.
Sudden for what, though?
What am I even implying here?
She's a lot lighter than I thought.
Know what?
I'm gonna quit basketball club.
Yeah?
It's just, I hadn't been to practice in a while anyway.
And now I'm forbidden from playing, so...
Forbidden? Talk about being harsh.
But, I gotta join some club, right?
Yeah.
Maybe I'll join the data processing club.
Yeah?
Would you say something?
I said, yeah, didn't I?
Are we still good?
Are we having an actual conversation?
Am I still breathing?
Double riding a bicycle like that is a serious breach of the law.
I'm going to contact your parents and your school.
Kiyotaro, how could you do this to me?
She was riding on that loner's bike.
Did he force her?
I had to quit my modeling career.
I'd never allow myself to do something like that.
Hey, Ichikawa, do you prefer the standard coffee flavor poppiko
or the white sour ones more?
Oh, the coffee ones?
Ooh.
Afraid of a little bit of change, aren't you?
Huh?
The light's green.
Right.
I've always been sick.
There's just something wrong with my head.
Thanks, bet I felt heavy.
No, not a bit.
Guess I've no choice but to give you this.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Don't act that surprised.
Okay.
Here.
Uh.
Was that the right way to react?
See ya.
Maybe I should raise my hand higher?
All right, class, listen up.
Apparently someone threw away some sort of snack food wrapper in the library trash.
Now, all of you know it's against the rules to bring in snacks.
Playing with your eraser?
What are you, a third grader?
If we're having this talk now after the whole Puruche incident, then I bet...
Yamada?
Huh?
Any idea who it could be?
You should have been ready for this!
I never threw anything in the trash, so it couldn't be me.
Yamada?
I want you in the teacher's office after class.
What?
Such a dumbass.
I am?
But why?
An idiot through and through, huh?
This could be a problem, though.
Our teacher was busy, so Yamada's off the hook until next week.
But if she can't bring snacks in anymore, that means she won't drop by the library.
I'm exhausted.
I had to work five days in a row, and now I'm here babysitting.
You're the one who dragged me out to this place.
Thanks for coming with me.
Darling brother.
Don't give me that!
I wanted to use this time to think up a plan, too.
If anyone from my class caught me here with this idiot, I'd just die.
Wait.
Stop thinking like that.
Every time you do,
it always comes true!
Okay, Abel, you're right.
What's wrong?
Enough of you!
Gotta admit, I was surprised.
Didn't think no one would hit on us.
I'm sorry.
Does anyone ever actually hit on you when you're out in public?
I kind of want to know the answer to that.
Well, someone did come up and talk to anyone.
But it doesn't count, because it was just some random relative of mine.
I can't hear a word she's saying.
Chill out with the seasoning pack!
Hey, little brother.
You sure that's enough?
You look like some girl on a diet with just a salad.
Shut your mouth, you idiot!
Here, a present from your big sis.
You're still a growing boy, after all.
Huh?
Fine.
I'm gonna go buy something else to eat.
Welcome, how can I help you?
I needed to get out of there.
Why do my worst nightmares always come true?
Hey!
Wow.
Watch it.
Is she trying to pick a fight?
Was that your sister sitting with you?
She's super cute.
She's always trying to do everything for me.
It's dumb.
Oh, really?
I wish she could be my friend.
Hmm?
So she could do everything for you?
Sheesh.
I'm kind of jealous.
I'm an only child, you see.
Yeah, I could have guessed.
Everyone says that.
What are you gonna get?
Seasoned chicken.
Oh, copying me.
Busted dude!
She looks so grown up out of her uniform.
Maybe I'll go ahead and get something as well.
Ooh, I want some soft serve.
Oh shoot, my wallet is upstairs.
Were you not getting something?
I needed to pee.
The bathrooms are all upstairs though.
Oh, whoopsie!
Imagine that!
See ya!
Thanks for waiting.
Sheesh.
Wait, did she come down just to talk to me?
Are you ready to order?
Uh, um, the seasoned chicken and...
No, why would she?
I bet she really just didn't know where the bathrooms were.
Will that be all then?
No, um, let me get...
What did I buy this for?
It's not like I could give it to her.
Uh, uh, uh, this is...
Well, copied me again, huh?
No, I gotta...
She smells so nice.
Yamada's still not here?
I bet she completely forgot.
Hey!
Seriously?
Quit popping up like that!
What's the matter?
You need to talk to a teacher or something?
N-no, I was just passing by here is all.
Then come in with me.
Why is that?
Because I'm scared.
That's got nothing to do with me.
Are you sure?
Okay, maybe not...
nothing.
Ichikawa?
Why are you here?
Um, just here to observe, sir.
And to keep things totally transparent.
Oh, I see then.
To make sure I don't pull any dirty tricks on you, huh?
Huh, I guess you can be smart sometimes.
You know very well that snacks aren't allowed anywhere on the premises.
Who brought any snacks into school?
You think it was me?
Listen here.
I already know about the incident that happened in the science lab.
Sir, Miss Yamada never admitted to bringing in any snacks.
What are you saying?
Sir, you're trying to find out who it was that threw away that snack wrapper back in the library.
And you're asking whether or not it was Yamada who did it.
All Miss Yamada did say was that she did not do it.
Oh, she only answered that way because she is bringing in some snacks.
Normally you wouldn't word it like that, just say so if you weren't bringing any in.
Yes, normally you wouldn't.
What?
Normally someone would know what you were truly asking.
But some people just answer the question that's asked.
Sir, which group do you think Miss Yamada falls in?
Maybe, but...
Miss Yamada didn't throw the wrapper away and never said she brought snacks in.
And that's that.
BAM!
Got him.
That's all I came to say.
Bye.
Ichikawa.
No good, huh?
Impressive!
Never seen you talk this much before.
I'm happy.
Glad to see it.
Give me a break!
Not sure I really liked your logic there, but thanks.
It was just a bit of sophism.
Let me give you some candy.
Which one do you want?
Only one of those is even candy!
You're such a dorky little kid.
What?
Oh, we should...
Talk like friends.
N-not like how we talk is a big deal or anything.
Happy dinner.
Wow.
What happened?
You didn't get a little cold, but nothing!
This is a condom project.
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
初音ミク